♪ urgent, dramatic music ♪
Well,
we got your boy in Ukraine.
Not 48 hours later,
senior case officer
overseeing the mission had
two Russian contract agents
at her fucking
front door.
You round-tripping for Russia?
These fucking Russians,
they're a different breed.
Don't you fucking call me that.
That's what you are.
You're a fucking Russian.
I'm calling a family meeting.
Okay, let me have it.
We want you to quit.
Girls,
I'm a soldier,
and a soldier's job
is to fight until the soldier
is unable to fight
or until the fight is over.
I'm sorry this followed me home.
Your fucking people
came after me and my family!
Well, you know what they say.
A soldier's oath is
his family's oath.
My number's in it.
We start now.
♪ tense, eerie music ♪
The one thing...
that made the United States
so dangerous for so long...
...was that your people believed
in the fantasy of freedom.
But now...
that fantasy is fading.
In its place, the reality
that man is not meant
to be free.
We're a pack, like the wolf.
And like the wolf,
we need a leader.
His rule can be just,
it can be fair...
...but it must be absolute.
Your people are waking up
to that reality.
They don't know
it's what they need yet.
First they must lose
everything, all order.
Then they're gonna throw away
their freedom like trash
and beg for leader.
You already did it once
with COVID.
One bad call
shattered the illusion
that your independence is yours.
Is that what Russia has, huh?
A just leader?
Fucking career KGB agent
turned dictator?
You really think
that moron's a pack leader, huh?
You're getting the shit
kicked out of you
by the most obsolete, inept
and corrupt army
in all of Central Europe.
You want to know why that is?
'Cause we put a few hundred
boots on the ground
and we stopped
your punk asses cold.
Your entire shitty, half-witted,
convict-ass army...
...using the same weapons
the Taliban shoved up
your fucking asshole in 1980.
Afghanistan is using
your weapons now.
The weapons left behind...
...when you ran away.
This birdbath water drip.
It's a nasty trick.
I might have to steal that.
But spare me
the fucking lectures
on failed societies.
Okay? Russia disproved
every political theory
Marx ever made
in spectacular fashion.
You even managed
to kill more of your own people
than the whole fucking German
army ever did in the process.
A failed monarchy,
a failed democracy,
failing as a dictatorship.
The only reason
why Russia still exists
is because nobody wants
to take away
that frozen shithole from you.
But I get it.
You got to go through
the motions and try to flip me.
Be my guest.
I'll just lay back and listen.
This is not my job.
Once we get you home,
I'll show you my job.
And I am expert.
♪ tense, dramatic music ♪
♪ dramatic, haunting music ♪
♪ ominous music ♪
We missed.
QRF retrieved her beacon.
Her beacon, not her?
- That is correct.
- Any indication
- where she is now?
- NSA has
a database of vehicles
that have entered
and exited the Russian embassy.
We're cross-referencing that
with state police
license readers.
What's that going to accomplish?
By now, an SVR case officer
is almost certainly
overseeing her movements.
Any senior level case officer
is going
to have diplomatic immunity.
We are cross-referencing
diplomatic plates
with PD database
to see if any were
in the proximity
of her last known location.
What is their objective?
Logistically, it's to get her
out of the States,
get her back to Russia,
where I assume
they're going to reach out to
negotiate a trade with Yurimov.
And Yurimov is in Gitmo, right?
Yes, sir.
Can I assume your officers
have interviewed Mr. Yurimov?
- You can, sir.
- And did anything
of value come out
of those interviews?
Yeah.
We are investigating
the information
that he's provided thus far.
We expect it
to appear useful on the surface,
but most of the information
is likely planted
with the purpose
of it being offered, sir.
- Of course.
- Any valuable intel
that Yurimov holds, the Russians
are likely altering as we speak.
Talk us through
the worst-case scenario here.
Worst-case?
How bad
can this fucking thing get?
SVR has some knowledge
of the Lioness program.
They even have
some limited knowledge
of, uh, specific operations,
but they don't have definitive
proof of those operations.
Joe can provide that.
What intelligence value
- do past operations hold?
- None to speak of,
but that's not the purpose.
What would be the purpose?
Knowledge
of specific Lioness targets
could be released publicly,
creating severe
diplomatic consequences for us
with various strategic partners
in the Middle East-- the Saudis,
Qatar, UAE, Egypt.
It would greatly compromise us
in the region.
And the political damage
domestically, that's...
that is very difficult
to predict.
I mean,
what position does the UN take?
What is the position
of Congress?
Do they see this
as an opportunity
to blame the administration?
Based on the current climate,
I would certainly think so.
This is the worst-case scenario?
- No, ma'am.
- It gets worse?
Worst-case scenario is,
Russia does not release
the information.
Russia turns her over to Iran.
Iran releases the information,
tries her...
and finds her guilty.
I need a timeline.
She is most likely
still in the D.C. area.
Moving her by vehicle is risky.
Every time they do so,
they increase the chances
that we intercept.
They're gonna need
to get her on a plane
out of the area
and then another plane
out of the United States.
24 to 36 hours,
and she is likely
on a plane to Russia indirectly.
Eh, possibly Cuba, but
that's unlikely, given the fact
that we are monitoring
every aircraft in that region.
We have FBI and CED at Dulles,
Reagan, National College Park,
- Manassas--
- A more reliable
method of moving human cargo,
albeit slower, is by ship.
We are moving resources
to the ports of Virginia,
Baltimore, Philadelphia.
JSOC has units in Wilmington,
Morehead City, and
the Inland Port in Charlotte.
I think it's time
to inform the president.
I... disagree.
What?
Respectfully, I disagree, sir.
I think the fewer people that
know this, the better for now.
POTUS is going to be inclined
to inform Senate Intelligence,
and then Senate Intelligence
informs 700 staffers,
and then we've just told
the whole world.
Find her, Byron.
Fallout from this shit
is limitless.
We are aware, sir.
- Do it.
- Thank you.
Great.
Thank you.
This thing is headless
right now.
You get to Quantico
and take it over.
Bring in Delta, Ground Branch, everyone.
Yes, sir.
Yes. Okay, NSA has a hit.
- All right.
- Yankee Romeo
656759.
Seven, five, nine. All right.
Where are you, you motherfucker?
Okay, I got him on 16th, uh,
about three hours ago.
495 to the 95.
Find me a ping on a tower,
Bobbo.
Working on it.
195. Oh, he's going
- to the fucking airport.
- Damn it.
- Get me a cell, Bobbo.
- Working on it.
All right,
he took, uh, he took Friendship.
All right, I got him.
Is he still there?
- Mm-hmm.
- All right,
he's in a hangar
right fucking here.
Okay, we have a location.
Coordinates coming your way.
I need the plane assigned to
that hangar and that location.
And how the fuck
do we approach?
They'll have eyes on
the second we land on the FBO.
Hey, can you put us on the roof?
- You got a bird?
- Are you kidding me?
I need a Little Bird
from Air Branch.
ATC got to clear us
a flight path to location.
Okay, got it.
Okay, stay in contact.
♪ urgent, dramatic music ♪
Down, down, down!
- Down now! Down now!
- Down, down, down, down!
- Get on the ground.
- On the fucking ground!
On the ground, turn over!
Face down now!
- Is she still here?!
- Is who still here?
Give me your fucking hands.
Give me
your fucking hands, bitch.
Piece of shit.
Fuck.
- Bobby.
- Yeah.
This motherfucker.
Blood on the floor?
Looks like you missed a spot,
motherfucker!
We have diplomatic immunity.
Do we look like
the fucking police to you?
Fuck, Kyle!
We're not here to arrest you.
You got to give me something,
or I'm gonna fucking kill you
and I'm gonna dump your body
in the Potomac.
Tail number.
Better kill me.
Hey, Kyle. Kyle.
Let's just have CED come get
these motherfuckers
and take the intel back to base.
We're good.
I don't think you understand
what they'll do to her
when they get her
out of this country.
Fuck.
Tail number.
Uh, N, five...
...six...
...five...
K, J.
November 565 Kilo
Juliet.
Okay, tracking's being blocked.
I'm gonna check with BW ATC.
Yeah, I need manifest.
November 565 Kilo Juliet.
Was inbound from PHL.
Arrived BWI 10:53 for refuel.
Departed 11:07 VFR at 8500.
Fuck.
Departed
11:07 BWI VFR at 8500.
At least
you were telling the truth.
Land the bird and pick us up.
What about these guys?
It's their fucking mess,
they'll clean it up.
Who are they going to tell?
Let's fucking go.
Police up the intel, let's move.
Fuck.
Let's move!
♪ up-tempo dramatic music ♪
No, I need every tower.
Every tower's flight log.
What do you have?
They loaded her onto
a Challenger 300.
It has
a 3,400-nautical mile radius.
That gives us Cuba, that
gives us Mexico and Venezuela.
We have jets right now
off the coast of Florida
and a fourth fleet that's
scrambled in the Caribbean.
They're going to need
mission clarity if they engage.
- You tracking the flight?
- They're below 18,000.
I can't.
The locator's been disabled,
and there is no flight plan
that was submitted.
She's on a jet.
Destination unknown.
Transponder disabled.
Air assets are searching now.
We're going to need guidance
if contact is made.
If located in U.S. airspace,
our jets maneuver
to force landing.
If found in international,
they are to engage.
Can I get a word, ma'am?
Word, please?
What is it?
My understanding of the ROE
is fire if fired upon
- or credible threat is present.
- You understand correctly.
Well, that motherfucker
right there just
executed a Russian
intelligence officer
while he was immobilized
in front of us.
And I don't feel like fucking
going to jail for Kyle.
Let me explain what happens
when they get her
to a secure location.
They either torture the name
of every
case officer, every safe house,
every operation,
every asset,
everything that she knows,
endangering the lives
of fuck knows how many operators
we have deployed.
Our FOBs in Ukraine,
our travel routes.
Every goddamn thing.
Or, and even worse,
they drop her off in Tehran,
where she's paraded around
until she's tried
and stoned to death
or hung or shot.
Or worse still,
Iran hands her over
to Hezbollah,
which paralyzes us
in the region
'cause now
they have a female U.S. citizen
convicted of Iranian war crimes.
Now the pressure's on Israel,
'cause Hezbollah's going
to demand
that Tel Aviv unlock
every prison door
and let their fucking army out.
What do we do, huh?
What do we give up
when Israel doesn't do that?
This is
how presidents lose elections,
how parties lose majority
in the House and the Senate,
how the UN starts
war crime tribunals,
'cause everybody
in the fucking world,
minus the UK, wants us weaker.
And the way the UK's going,
they're going to want it, too.
So, yeah,
I treated this like war.
And it is fucking war.
Yeah, that all sounds good,
except there's a dead body
in the airplane hangar.
Look, I'm no homicide detective,
but it sure seems like
a fucking execution to me.
All right, all right,
who's going to report it?
Huh?
Two Russian spies
who kidnapped a U.S. citizen?
That body was gone
before we even got back here.
And it ain't ever getting found.
It's still
a fucking execution, Kyle.
I got the tail number, didn't I?
Adhere to the ROEs in place.
Do you understand me?
I'm treating all of this
as hearsay until evidence
to the contrary
starts popping up.
And if it does, Kyle,
you are on your own.
Until that time,
both of you stand down
and go find our fucking girl.
Yes, ma'am.
Double agent in WitPro?
- Yeah.
- Bring her back.
All of their supply routes
have been in place for years.
Safe houses, travel routes,
all of it.
And just like ours,
none of it is written down.
It's memorized.
She's gonna know.
I don't have the juice
to make that call.
I will make it. Walk with me.
You have relaxed ROEs
due to your status in the SMU.
They don't have the same.
Your rules are different
to theirs.
Don't play
outside the lines with them.
I need someone who can play
outside the lines.
They're coming.
♪ dramatic music ♪
CIA Deputy Director Westfield
is here for you, sir.
Send him in.
- Go ahead, please.
- Thank you.
Byron.
Ten minutes.
We missed her
by ten fucking minutes.
Hmm.
We've identified the plane, though.
- Planes are hard to hide.
- Yeah.
They're trying
to get her out of the country?
Very much so.
- No word from Darchiev?
- No.
Oh, they're not
gonna acknowledge
until she's on Russian soil.
Then, of course, they'll call
- and want to make a trade.
- Mm.
We worry
they might want something else.
Like what?
There's been a series
of embarrassments for 'em.
Ukrainian intelligence officer
infiltrating SVR.
Our ability to take Yurimov from
Russian-controlled territory.
It's a massive,
massive intelligence failure
on their part.
Our operations and assistance
have effectively shut down
the Russian offensive
for almost three years.
I worry
they want to embarrass us back.
I mean, they haven't accused us
of having Yurimov.
They haven't even
asked the question.
They are that embarrassed.
Joe's theater's been
the Middle East
for the entirety of her career.
She doesn't even have relevant
intelligence to give them,
but what she could provide Iran
and the opportunities
that she presents
for them and their proxies?
If Russia just hands her off,
it becomes the sole focus
of your foreign policy without
leverage until it's resolved.
And getting her back is going
to be very, very expensive.
Got an awful lot of problems.
You got any solutions?
We admit to having Yurimov.
We offer him back.
He's given us
no useful information,
and the only way to get
real information leaves him
in no condition to return.
We justify taking him
by claiming fear
of a new Russian offensive.
We use it
to negotiate a ceasefire.
We don't really give a shit
if we get one,
but it gives us
the justification
for the operation
in the first place.
That doesn't offer me
any leverage.
They could release that
to the press.
Now I got 60 Minutes
doing a story
on U.S. intelligence and
military operations in Ukraine.
The leverage is in the threat
that comes next.
If she's released to a proxy,
that presence
increases dramatically,
as does its purpose.
Well...
...this I'll have to discuss
with the president
and Senate Intelligence
and the Joint Chiefs.
I may point out
that none of them is aware
that we ran a capture mission
in Russia.
You're saying
it's time for that?
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry to say,
it's time for that.
Okay.
Step outside.
Give me a minute, please.
Yes, sir.
I need him.
No, I need him now.
Mr. President?
We have a situation.
You're late for school, girls.
Nope, I got their assignments
for the week.
They'll do 'em here
and then I'll turn 'em in.
Why would you do that?
Because when their soldier
escorts decided to treat
road construction like
a fucking ambush in Syria...
- Neal.
- I made a judgment call
that dying in a car wreck
was more detrimental
to their grade point average
than doing their homework here
in our fake home.
Can I have a word with you?
Sure.
Guys, come on.
Please don't fight.
This is bad enough
without you two fighting.
We're not fighting, honey,
but serious situations
require serious conversations,
and that's what we're having.
- They're gonna fight.
- 100%.
What are you doing?
If everything's going to hell,
then it's going to hell
with me eating ice cream.
All right, give me some.
♪ slow, gentle music ♪
- You have surgery today?
- Nope. Punted the day.
I want to stay with the girls.
One of my team is gonna take you
out to the range.
I want you familiar enough
with a pistol.
Joe, that is
completely unnecessary.
It's an overreaction,
I know, but I'd rather
you prepared for a fight
that never comes...
- Joe.
- ...than find yourself
in a fight
you're not prepared for.
We have been through this.
I took an oath,
you took an oath.
- Yes. Uh-huh.
- Our oaths couldn't be more
- different, but I still took it.
- Yeah. "Do no harm."
- I know that oath.
- Yes, that's the one.
I'm not asking you to shoot
one of your patients, Neal.
- The oath is to humanity, Joe.
- Yes, well, your oath is naive
because only doctors are
adhering to that oath.
The rest of the world
is using harm
like it's a form of currency.
- Your world.
- The world, Neal.
- No, and judging
by the two people that showed up
at our fucking front door,
the world is here.
It doesn't matter how
it got here. It's here, Neal.
And it seems to me
that failing to protect yourself
and our two daughters
is a greater harm
than doing harm
to those that would harm them.
Can you just follow
the fucking logic to that?
Oh, I follow it.
- Just do it to pacify me, okay?
- Yeah.
The odds you'll ever use what
you learn are very slim, Neal.
Why don't I just take them
to my mother's?
'Cause you're safer here.
If I'm safer here, why
am I taking a gun class, Joe?
I love you.
- Love you, too.
- I love you.
Love you.
Bye, guys.
Yesterday evening
FBI counterintelligence agents
apprehended an agent...
- Is this you?
- ...of the Russian
Foreign Intelligence Service,
or SVR as it is known
to the intelligence community.
The U.S. Attorney's Office is
preparing espionage charges
stemming from evidence
implicating the agent
in both bribery schemes
and extortion schemes
against U.S. government officials,
as well as state and local
government officials...
I told you, babe,
don't believe the news.
You didn't answer my question.
I'm keeping my word, Neal.
And I'm solving the problem, okay?
Bye.
Wait, wait, Joe.
I'm not mad.
I know that it seems that I am.
I'm not.
I'm scared, Joe.
I'm scared for you.
I'm scared for our daughters.
I'm scared that we live
in a world where this can happen
and how it became that world.
It's just...
it's very disheartening.
The very first
political assassination...
...was a pharaoh named Teti
in 23rd century BC.
One can argue Christ was also
a political assassination.
James I of Scotland,
Spencer Perceval,
Lincoln, Franz Ferdinand,
Sadat, Gandhi,
Kennedy, King.
The world didn't
become this way, Neal.
It's always been this way.
♪ pensive music ♪
Go get 'em.
We getting in the game?
Yes.
And we're going
to trust this Russian?
- She's Ukrainian.
- Okay.
And we're going
to trust this Ukrainian?
We don't trust anybody.
♪ dramatic music ♪
Come on in, Joe.
- Word is out.
- I saw.
I want a very clear objective
for this operation.
Very clear and very specific.
Operation name is Treasure.
Our Ukrainian asset is Badger.
Your team is Hornet.
The SMU attachment is Spider.
SVR officers are Gold,
and their assets Silver.
Now, when Russian intelligence
makes contact
with a source and then develops
that source into an asset,
that asset's identity is shared
with SVR handlers
to prevent multiple handlers
working the same person.
Now, the handler and contact,
however, is not shared.
So Badger would know
within her network
who was being recruited,
but she doesn't know
- who recruited them.
- We feel like
today's announcements
will rattle assets
much more than it will
Russian intelligence.
We will place a Lioness
in close proximity to the assets
and offer them a way out
in exchange
for identifying the handler
controlling them.
- Define "a way out."
- That's up to you.
FBI, U.S. Attorney's Office,
and I assume
it's on a case-by-case basis.
U.S. Attorneys are gonna treat
a House of Representatives
staffer extorted
by some stripper
very different than they will
a software engineer
from Lockheed
who takes a hundred grand
for hard data.
Well, whatever you offer has
to be vague.
We aren't in Marrakech.
These people are going
to hire attorneys,
and they are going
to use the press
to their advantage
any way they can.
And most SVR officers have cover
as state officials
with diplomatic immunity.
All we can do is
detain and deport.
Just be mindful of that.
- Yes, sir.
- Will do.
I want thorough
updates, and I want 'em often.
And by often, I mean daily.
- You'll get 'em.
- You got it.
Thank you.
Deputy ambassador reached out.
Hmm.
It's not surprising.
- He wants to meet.
- What time? Where?
Seven. Where do you think?
Care to run interference?
How much interference?
Not that they notice.
Ah, this is
making me feel
like the Cold War.
I wouldn't know.
I was still in school.
So was I.
It's just how I imagine it.
♪ dramatic, suspenseful music ♪
You got to shave all the way?
- I do what I'm told, brother.
- I don't know.
What's your cover?
Chief of staff for this guy.
You... you don't look
like a chief of staff.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, he don't look
like a Democrat either.
The fuck is that supposed
to mean?
Hey, hey, hey, man.
You're looking
in the fucking mirror.
Tell me what you see.
All right? 'Cause I'll tell you
what the whole
fucking world sees.
The world sees a guy
who looks like
he just rebuilt a carburetor.
Well, that's why
I'm shaving, bud.
Shaving ain't gonna help.
Oh, no?
What's your cover, huh?
If it ain't creepy middle school
gym teacher, you're fucked.
Gym fucking teacher.
Oh, yeah,
you think that's funny, huh?
- I do.
- What's your cover?
Oh, boys, boys, boys,
please, please.
I'm just a defense contractor
putting his feet up
on the main stage.
Fucking lucky bastard.
Yeah, well, uh, I'm also
putting your hard-earned
tax dollars to work.
What an asshole.
Thank you for your service.
Are you aware you're an asshole?
I fucking look good
when I clean up, don't I?
Don't I?
You look
like a bowling champion.
♪ Hello, sun, goodbye, rain ♪
♪ Gimme shelter... ♪
Okay.
Oh, yeah, no, that's...
Lot of sparkle.
This'll work.
This is what I'm talking about.
Look at this shit.
Yeah.
Look at that shit.
- I can't see with your big ass.
- Shit.
I need some of this mirror
action, too, damn it.
Well, I don't know about him,
but you're not fooling anybody.
Man,
she ain't trying to fool nobody.
That's right.
I'm just trying to help you out
in case you get in a bind.
You know, there's a lovely
little leopard dress over there,
Kyle. Look good on you.
Oh, I'll try it on
for you later, if you like.
Hey.
- Nothing about this is funny.
- Right, boss.
Bobby.
Sorry, boss, I'm-I'm,
I'm trying. Trying, I swear.
Try harder.
Goddamn it.
Man, come on, boss.
You can't tell me
that's not the reason
they put faces on milk cartons.
You can't tell me that.
Oh, you have jokes?
- You have jokes.
- Oh, baby face.
Look at that.
Ooh, it feels so smooth.
Um, how about a vodka soda?
Heavy on the soda.
The usual.
Thank you.
- You want to start a tab?
- No, I will pay cash.
Thank you.
♪ mysterious music ♪
White shirt, blue tie,
end of the bar.
Excuse me.
No problem.
Sorry we're late.
It's fine.
We've been enjoying the show.
Putting on
quite the show yourself.
You don't even
hide yours anymore.
Just send in soldiers.
Yeah, well, when you show up
at my case officer's house
posing as law enforcement,
we get a little jumpy.
Thank you.
A sparkling, please?
Was that your little dance
this morning?
You call some cowboys
from who-knows-where
Russian intelligence?
Think that was us?
I know it was you.
How? How do you know?
I expect your politicians
to be bad liars,
- but from you, I expect more.
- No, thank you.
I've told you no lies, Maxim.
- Uh, not one.
- An SVR
intelligence officer
contacted a CIA
senior case officer
offering information
regarding SVR sources,
uh, strategic information,
contingencies, capabilities.
Not the bullshit
you've planted in Trojan horses,
but legitimate information and
assets, both here and abroad.
See? That is how you lie.
And for what do they do this?
What do they gain?
We're not Soviet Union,
they don't need to defect.
If they want to stay here,
they already have a passport,
they apply for a visa,
and they stay.
They quit their job with us
and start a new job.
With you.
Thank you.
Russian citizens
have fought in your army,
in your special forces.
We're a free country now, too.
Debatable.
No debate.
And not the reason you call me.
You're fishing.
Why? What new game
you think we're playing?
You tell me.
I'm not wasting my time
playing this game.
You don't have anyone.
If you had somebody,
we would know.
If you turned one,
you would never tell us,
and you would never
tell the news.
So... what the fuck
are you doing?
What the fuck
are you fishing for?
♪ ominous music ♪
Let's talk about Ukraine.
- Sure.
- What do you think
you're doing there?
Protecting an ally
from an authoritarian state.
Well, Ukraine is our state.
It was part of Russia
since before you were a nation.
Now it's all gangsters
and thieves.
It's our Sicily, you understand?
It relies on payoffs and bribes
from Europe, from you,
from your politicians,
your companies.
It was breadbasket of Europe.
It was our industrial center
for 250 years.
This is not your war.
It's our war.
I don't choose the wars, Maxim.
You know that.
But you fight it anyway.
I do what I'm told.
We lost something
that is very valuable
to our president.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Mm.
We think maybe it was stolen,
this thing.
Maybe...
you know where it is?
We're gonna need
more information.
We'd be happy to help you.
Just need to know
what we're looking for.
You know.
What do we know?
They would tell you.
They would have to.
Listen, if we can be helpful,
we'll be helpful.
Now, we'll want something
in return, but...
you have to ask for the favor.
- Mm-hmm.
- Byron,
I can't ask.
But
if you find it, you'll know,
and we'll want it back.
Yeah.
Fair enough.
Have fun with
your pretend prize.
Run along now.
Oh...
Guess... I guess
they think
it's our first day on the job.
Can't blame him for trying.
I'll see you at the office.
Mm. Sure.
Can I do another one of those?
- Thank you.
- My tab.
- No, it's-- it's my-- it's
- No, it's oka--
a company tab.
It's not even my tab,
- so it's fine.
- Oh.
Thanks.
It's fine. Thank you,
- though.
- Sure, sure.
Your company give out per diem
in cash?
No, it... No. I, um,
I actually had
my company card stolen
- last year, so...
- Ah, yeah.
- Yeah. Once bitten, twice shy.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
What's your business?
I am a consultant.
So, a lobbyist.
Guilty.
What firm?
ADI.
- Okay. No.
- It's a--
- It's--
- That's... that's my field.
- Oh.
- I'm with Northrop.
You don't have
that engineer look about you.
- No?
- Mm-mmm. No.
Sales.
- Okay. Okay,
- Yes.
- that makes sense then.
- Okay.
That makes sense.
- Mm-hmm. Mm.
- Charles.
- Oh, that's funny.
- What?
It's not gonna be hard
to remember. Charlie.
- No.
- Yeah.
- Really? You're Charlie?
- Char-Charlie.
Excuse me.
♪ suspenseful music ♪
♪ All my friends,
so sweet and innocent ♪
♪ The story never ends ♪
♪ Woke up
and now I think I'm dreamin'♪
♪ Sunny days,
it's such a pretty place ♪
♪ I see your smiling face ♪
♪ Woke up
and now I think I'm dreamin'♪
♪ All my friends,
so sweet and innocent ♪
♪ The story never ends ♪
♪ Woke up and now
I think I'm dreamin'♪
♪ Now I think I'm dreamin'... ♪
They're getting
a lot of attention,
- boss.
- Yeah.
♪ Sunny days,
it's such a pretty place ♪
♪ I see your smiling face ♪
♪ Woke up
and now I think I'm dreamin'♪
♪ All my friends,
so sweet and innocent ♪
♪ The story never ends ♪
♪ Woke up
and now I think I'm dreamin'♪
♪ Sunny days,
it's such a pretty place ♪
♪ I see your smiling face ♪
♪ Woke up
and now I think I'm dreamin'♪
♪ All my friends,
so sweet and innocent ♪
♪ The story never ends ♪
♪ Woke up
and now I think I'm dreamin'♪
♪ Now I think I'm dreamin'... ♪
We're on one.
Work him.
♪ All my friends,
so sweet and innocent ♪
♪ The story never ends ♪
♪ Woke up and now I think ♪
♪ I'm dreamin' ♪
Can I get a beer?
Light blue shirt.
Look for the mark.
♪ Sunny days,
it's such a pretty place ♪
♪ I see your smiling face ♪
♪ Woke up
and now I think I'm dreamin'♪
♪ All my friends,
so sweet and innocent ♪
♪ The story never ends,
woke up and now I think...♪
Hey, can I have a vodka soda,
heavy on the soda?
♪ Such a pretty place,
I see your smiling face ♪
♪ Woke up
and now I think I'm dreamin'♪
♪ All my friends,
so sweet and innocent ♪
♪ The story never ends ♪
♪ Woke up and now
I think I'm dreamin'...♪
That your girlfriend?
Oh, we're just having fun.
Sure looks like fun.
It is fun.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I could use some fun.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Come on.
♪ Now I think I'm dreamin' ♪
♪ All my friends,
so sweet and innocent ♪
♪ The story never ends ♪
♪ Woke up and now I think
I'm dreamin'...♪
This looks
like small potatoes, boss.
You got to get past 60,000 bees
to find the queen, Bobby.
♪ Now I think I'm dreamin'... ♪
♪ pensive music ♪
My gosh, you're...
You're all grown up.
Is your dad around?
Dad!
Your daughter didn't seem
happy to see me.
She-She's not happy in general.
They know something's up.
Did you tell them
what I told you to say?
They can tell when I'm lying.
It's not one of my skills.
Doesn't feel like good news,
Kaitlyn.
It's not.
We're close, but, um...
we're still a step behind,
and time's not on our side.
So I'm gonna share with you
probably more than I should.
Um, there's three possibilities.
One, we beat the clock,
and she is home in a few days.
Two, the clock wins,
and this could take time.
- Real time.
- Well, define "real time."
Months.
Longer.
To negotiate the trade
of an officer
who is accused of espionage,
if that's what
they accuse her of.
It involves divulging
very privileged,
very precious information.
Information that can...
...that can put other officers
in danger.
And put our strategic partners
and the military presence
overseas
in harm's way.
These are
very delicate negotiations.
They can be greatly influenced
by any number of factors
beyond our control.
And what's three?
She doesn't come back
with three.
Prepare for the third.
That way,
if it doesn't come true,
relief will be your reward.
And if it does,
you're prepared.
And you can be there
for your children.
Her children.
I am so sorry
to do this to you, but...
she would want you
to be ready, Neal.
Yeah.
Which one do you think it is?
In your gut?
There's too many variables
to rely on instinct.
- What the fuck does that mean?
- It means
I don't know.
I don't fucking know.